[ED]
Yoo-hoo!
Where's this?
What is this?
What the hell!
Miyazaki Bougainvillea Airport!
Yay!
This is awesome! Palm trees!
It's warm!
Why did I come to Miyazaki?
At the evacuation meeting, I had suggested that I would like to go to Miyazaki to do Mukyo.
And just falling in love is boring, isn't it?
So I asked them to let me go, and I came!
Yay!
I will accompany you!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
But Haruharu told Dr. Lovemeal that he shines with his watch.
This year, you know, maybe this time.
That's right!
I think I will show a little shine Yamashita.
I'm looking forward to it!
Shall we walk a little? We've come all this way.
Is everyone in?
Yes, everyone's in.
Yay!
There are so many flowers.
Pink!
My psyllium-colored leaves!
It's a leaf.
I'm taking a walk.
It says "Sunrise in Japan" with flowers.
Japanese sunrise!
Yay!
Pretty!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
I found it!
Now I'm going to go to MRT Miyazaki Broadcasting Corporation! Now, I would like to go to MRT Miyazaki Broadcasting Co.
They've been broadcasting next year since January.
I'm very happy.
Let's go, Mr. Miyazaki.
Let's go say hello! Let's go say hello!
It says here in front of NRT's building
Can you see it?
This one!
Here they come.
What's that? Who's there?
I told you!
Good morning!
Hi, I'm Yamazaki!
Thank you very much!
Please give me your best regards!
My name is Yamazaki, announcer of Yamazaki Broadcasting Corporation.
Please!
The other day, I was on YouTube for the broadcast decision.
Just connect it to the 4th floor behind this car.
I see!
And I'm happy to announce it!
Thank you very much!
Please wear the T-shirt!
And please wear the T-shirt!
Thank you very much!
Since you came all the way to NRT
I'd like to take you all somewhere.
Where is it?
The company's studio is over here.
This is NRT, and from the first to the third floor, there's a commercial facility.
I'd like to take you all to a corner of the shopping center.
It's just over there.
Over there?
There's a booth.
Booth?
Right around the corner from Mini-Plaza. It's just around the bend on Mini-Pla.
That's right.
There's actually something that's been here for about four years.
What is it?
It's right this way!
Oh, wait, I found it!
It's been here for four years?
Do you remember?
Yes, I remember!
This is actually called the Hinatazaka Booth.
Oh, I'm so glad!
You've had this booth here for a long time?
Yes, I have.
What? !
Actually, we've been posting messages from our fans here at the sun.
We have a booth where we can deliver the messages from the fans to the members.
We had a booth for this project.
The Sun of Miyazaki and others
When the sun comes to Miyazaki from all over Japan
It has become a place where people from all over the country can stop by when they come to Miyazaki.
I'm so happy!
Look at this!
The new kids from the last poster have come back.
Oh, wow!
They put it up properly.
With new feet.
Can we paint this now?
Is that okay?
It's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
By all means, go ahead and do it.
I don't have it at this time either.
Oh, is that so?
That's why I want to draw it.
I'm the president of Miyazaki.
Double Southern
Thank you very much.
Please come and see it. Please come and see us!
Please do.
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle!
Miyazaki Broadcasting Corporation has been broadcasting our in-flight program.
I wanted to thank you for that.
I was wondering if I could meet the person in charge.
That's fine.
There's a department called the programming department that makes the TV listings.
I'll take you to their activities.
Thank you very much.
I'll come in.
Yes, please.
It's right this way.
Thank you very much.
Please, come in.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
My name is Ogata. I'm from the Miyazaki Broadcasting Co.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you for coming to Miyazaki.
Thank you very much.
I'll be happy to greet you.
We are
We are Hyugaizaka 46.
We look forward to meeting you.
I wonder if I'll be able to see you live.
Thank you very much.
Let's meet again at Hyuuga-zaka!
Miyazaki Broadcasting Corporation is broadcasting the show.
Thank you very much.
I'm very happy to hear that.
We had quite a good response, didn't we?
I was doing a lot of PR work.
I was doing a lot of PR and people from Miyazaki came.
Some people told us that we were going to start broadcasting from that episode. I was told that we were going to start broadcasting that episode.
Miyazaki was very excited.
Everyone is cheering for you.
Thank you very much.
I'm really looking forward to having the festival here in Miyazaki.
I'm really looking forward to having the festival here in Miyazaki, but in order to get the sun and the people of Miyazaki to know more and more about us...
I was wondering if I could be a part of a Miyazaki program or something like that.
I'm very grateful for your offer.
I can do that too.
I have a TV production manager named Yokoyama.
Yokoyama-san might be the first to get involved.
I think I'll be the first.
I look forward to working with you
I look forward to working with you.
My name is Yokoyama, I work in the TV Production Department.
Pleased to meet you.
Actually, we're Hyugaizaka 46.
We're Hyugaizaka 46, and we'd like to hold a festival in Miyazaki.
I'm the one who proposed it.
Do you have any suggestions on where we should hold the festival in Miyazaki?
Do you have any recommendations?
But if it's Hyuga-saka...
I think this is the only place to do it.
I think this is the only place.
I guess so.
By the way, how many people does it hold?
The stadium has a capacity of 30,000.
30,000?
It's the biggest in Miyazaki.
Is that right?
But 30,000?
That's amazing!
It's a dream!
I'm sure there are still many people who don't know about Hyuga.
I think there are still a lot of people who don't know about Hyuga.
I hope that many people in Miyazaki will get to know about Hyuga. I'd like to do some PR so that everyone in Miyazaki can get to know more about it.
I'd like to do some PR and stuff to let everyone in Miyazaki know about us.
I'm sorry, I just met you.
I'd really appreciate it if you could do it.
If you give me a chance...
I'll be ready to leave as soon as you come.
I'd like that very much.
You'd come?
No, no, no. It's important.
We have a lot of members now.
I'll see you every day.
Come on in.
Every day is a different day.
We'll visit you.
If we can really do a festival or something
I'd like to let the sun shine on Miyazaki.
Do you have any recommendations for that kind of thing?
There's a place called Aoshima.
Aoshima.
The scenery is amazing.
The scenery is amazing, and there are so many delicious foods.
It's getting a lot of attention again.
I see.
I want to go.
I wonder if I can go after this.
I'll try.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Qingdao said you'd recommend it to everyone.
Oh, this? It's called the Qingdao Picnic Club.
It's some kind of bike.
This one's nice, too.
There's a lot of them.
I'd like to make an appointment now.
It's my first time. Can you go? It's my first time. Can you go?
I'll be there. I'll introduce myself, tell you my name, and say that I'm filming for YouTube.
I'll tell them that I'd like to come and talk to you.
I'll let them know I'm coming.
Yes, I'll be there.
Thank you.
Don't you get a lot of phone calls?
Maybe if you make an appointment in person.
I mean, there's the going to the store thing, but...
Well, I'd like to make a phone call right away.
Thank you very much for your time.
I'm here in Miyazaki Prefecture for a YouTube shoot,
Is it OK to film for YouTube?
Yes, it is.
Certainly.
We are done.
How was it?
Welcome back.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It was all OK!
What did you say?
It was totally OK!
OK?
It was OK!
Thank you!
Thank you.
It's all OK!
You've got a lot of energy.
I could just feel the momentum.
Well, let's keep the momentum going.
Let's go.
Let's go! Let's go!
We have arrived at Aoshima Picnic Club!
Let's go!
Hello!
I'm the person you called earlier.
Thank you very much!
I hope you enjoy your day!
It's a great place!
Thank you!
The smell is so good! I can't get enough of it!
I saw that you offer bike rides,
Can I ride it today?
Sure.
It's decided!
I thought that was a no-no.
I'm so happy, so happy.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
It's wide!
It's great!
Look, look, look!
Nice place!
Nice view!
It's open!
Is this it? Perhaps.
Is that it?
An e-bike!
Yes, that's right.
An electric system.
Is it electric?
A bicycle.
It looks like a bike,
My goodness!
You can bring any one you like.
Really?
Then I'll choose this one.
This one! This girl!
I'll be here then.
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Let's be happy!
Oh, my God! Feels good! Fast!
It's awesome! There's an ocean! There's healing! Amazing!
Amazing!
Hey, did you do 5, Kami?
5 is awesome!
It goes on and on even though it's not 5!
It's fun! Are you with Haruharu?
Wait for me!
Hang in there!
It's the ocean all the way to the right!
It's so beautiful!
It's so beautiful! I want to share this view!
I want to share my eyes!
Miyazaki is the best!
Yoo-hoo!
Even if I'm not in love at all, I'm going so fast!
If I run 50 Meters in this, I'll be number 1 for sure!
Yes!
This is fun.
It's fun!
Wow! Here it comes!
It's true! Oh! I see it!
Oh! There it is!
Sunballetta Stadium Miyazaki!
So cute!
I wish I could go live here!
I'd love to do a live concert here!
Arrival
Here we are!
Hyuga Sanmarin Stadium Miyazaki Hyuga Sanmarin Stadium Miyazaki
Cute.
You two are going to fill this place with 30,000 people... customers.
Let's do our best to fill it up!
And do some PR.
It's like people from all over the country are coming here to Miyazaki.
Even if we have to split up since there's so many of us.
I hope we can go to many places this year.
Let's do our best to appeal and expand the circle of the sun!
I'll do my best.
So, that's it...
This is the store of Chimecafe!
This is Fruit Cafe Annex!
Please take a look.
It's open until 23:00 at night.
That's great!
I'm so excited!
Let's go eat.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Upstairs.
Oh, the door is so cute!
It's decorated with fruit.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Let's start here.
Parsate.
Strawberry perceto.
There's all kinds of strawberries.
Hugo nut parfait here.
Very nice.
It's the season, so now
It's the season now, isn't it?
The kumquats look delicious too!
Delicious!
We also have mangoes here.
But still...
You said it's the season.
I want to go for the Hugo-nut parfait! I would love to go to the Hugo Nut Parfait.
Yes, you do.
Let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
What about the other one?
vanillaAle x rose.
I'm curious.
It looks like a gold crown.
I'm curious about the whole thing.
I'd like to try these two.
Thank you very much.
I happen to have two kinds of these.
One mixed.
And one Huguenut parfait.
Please.
Yes, please.
Per ripe golden crown and
Per mixed red mixed style.
Thank you.
This is the one in the glass.
It happens to be a fully ripe golden crown.
The one on top happens to be an excellent one.
This one, please enjoy it with the skin on.
Please enjoy it with the skin intact.
And Huguenut mandarins.
Please enjoy them with their white skins intact.
Please eat with the white peel.
Bon appétit!
Just like the prefectures.
It's true.
Isn't that Gifu?
Look, it was just a customer.
Two hands.
This is what it looks like from above.
Three-dimensional.
This happens to be a fully ripe golden crown
parfait Parfait
Huganut parfait.
It's delicious.
Here you go.
After you.
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
Oh!
It's coming out.
Is it coming out?
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious!
Sweet.
Sweet?
Yes, it is.
It's so good.
It's got some acidity to it, but...
But it's high in sugar.
It's sweet.
Your turn.
Bon appétit.
Let's see if you can get it off.
You eat it with the skin on.
Huguenuts. Bon appétit.
Coffee is better.
No doubt about it.
Kansaise.
It's really good.
Really?
I can smell it.
Please eat.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit.
What's this?
It's delicious.
High sign.
Try this one, too.Try this one too.
Is this one sweet?
Try this one, too.
It's a gold crown!
It's out of focus.
Oh, sexy!
It's so bad, but it tastes sour.
It's sweet, but then it gets sour.
What's going on?
Arrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrty.
Yummy.
Let's all eat it now.
It's delicious.
It's like a chimecoffee after a meal, so...
It's light and easy to eat.
I didn't know brass band was so good!
I want to buy some to take home.
Let's go home!
Okay.
Thank you for the food
It was so delicious!
I'm so glad you let me shime!
So, that's it for today.
That's it!
We've done a lot, but today
I really moved and was active.
I got to visit with Mr. Yariko
And I got to say hello to you.
There's always tomorrow.
I'll have to decide whether I'm going to go with you at night or not.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.
See you later.
Good morning.
Second day.
It's the morning of the second day.
Where will you be? Please give us a hint. Where can I find them? Please give us a hint.
Oh, where are they?
Oh, the correct answer is,
Chu!
Here we are again at the Hyuga Sankyo Marie Stadium Miyazaki!
This is, you know, the place where Yurihyojin-kun has his camp!
I'm so happy! I'm so excited!
Today, I visited the camp and watched the practice,
I also got to go inside the Hinata-Sanmarie Stadium,
Is it like this?
I'm in! Yay!
Thank you very much! After practice,
I'm hoping to talk to some of the players,
I'm excited! You're the best!
I'm looking forward to it! I'm looking forward to it!
Let's go!
Wow! The wide sky!
People from Hyuhizaka? Why?
Teka? You're lying!
It's so big! Why is there a stream?
Oh, my God! Listen, everyone!
The moment you walk in, you'll see Teca flowing! I'm so happy!
Is there anything more exciting than that?
Surprise!
I'm so happy!
It's a surprise just to put it in there.
What do you think? Gentlemen!
It's huge!
But it's true, I'm from Hyogo, so I've never been to a stadium like this.
I've never been there before.
Oh, I see!
Yes, I have never been.
So, it's different from Yokohama Stadium, it's more open, isn't it?
It's fun! I want to play here!
Here, but, you know, maybe it's a dream!
It's a dream!
It says it's a sunny day, and how happy I'd be if I could perform on a sunny day! It says here that the sun is shining, and how happy I would be if I could perform on a sunny day!
The power of the sun is really great here.
It's amazing.
Good morning.
May I ask you a few questions?
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to say hello.
We're Hinatazaka 46.
Excuse me.
We're Hyuga-susan, and we're famous for performing at the stadium.
We're famous for performing at the Hyuga Sanmani Stadium.
I see.
Mr. Togo is from Miyazaki.
We call our fans Ohisama.
I'd love to hear your recommendations for places to go in Miyazaki.
Do you have any recommendations for places to go in Miyazaki?
I'd like to know what you ate growing up.
I'd like to know what Togo and I grew up eating.
This mayonnaise is from
Nobeoka
There's a jiroli shop called Ryu.
Jiroli?
The jiroli is so good!
Bonjiri is so good!
Bonjiri!
Bonjiri is the best I've ever had!
I want everyone to eat Bonjiri there!
I want to eat it!
I'm always looking at it.
This is my personal item
Miss Giannisse Mayonnaise
I've been going to the games, too.
That's your personal stuff!
It's mine.
I'm rooting for you, and I really hope you'll do well this season, too.
I'll be there if you're playing live!I'm going to see you live!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
We've already taken pictures.
You're welcome to come.
I look forward to seeing you and your fans.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This year.
This year's cup.
and
Yay!
Ishida's
Thank you so much!
So cool!
Become a Chains fan!
Thank you very much.
You're a fan
Thank you.
Nice to meet you again.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Good luck
This is the new hat from this year.
Ehh...
It's so cute!
If you are able to perform here
I want you to practice hard and build up your confidence.
Yes, sir!
Let's go for it!
Because you said you would come to our concert.
Let's do our best. good luck!
thank you very much
Oh, good
Fun.
Looks good on you. Haruharu looks good too.
Red Ball
Red Ball?
Please don't.
No Red Balls, please.
Can I come in here?
Bench.
Klondike.
Dorami's.
Good morning.
Thank you very much.
Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kumi Sasaki.
I am Mirei Sasaki.
I am Haruka Yamashita.
Pleased to meet you.
Coach Yano
I have been a Giants fan for a long time.
I sang a cheering song for Mr. Yano when he was a member of the Giants.
Yes, I saw the broadcast.
Oh, really?
Yes, yes.
Really?
Thank you very much.
I'm a voice actor with a flowery skin.
Can I sing the cheering song again here?
Is that okay?
Oh, is that okay? Oh, you don't mind?
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
You sure?
I'm a little nervous.
Okay, I'll go.
Kenji Yano, the spirited warrior.
Kenji Yano, get up.
Yes, yes, yes.
Engine
Oh my God, the lyrics just flew out
Light your heart on fire
For the sake of love, Kenji Yano, fight for your life
Kenji Sato Sei, thank you
This one, well, I kind of gave it to him as a favor
Thank you, Yakubi-chan
I'm so happy
The gummy bears are Mr. Sasaki's
I love gummy bears.
I love Gummi!
I'm so happy
I'm so happy.
Thank you so much!
You're too kind
Seikenji Sato loves bread!
Bread is only available in Kyushu, Miyazaki.
We don't sell it in Tokyo.
I see.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your time.
It's our dream to perform here at the Hyuga Sanmanin Stadium.
It's our dream to perform here at Hyuga Sanman Stadium.
That's right.
Really?
We'd love to have you come.
Sounds great.
It's gorgeous!
It's amazing.
All at once. All at once
Even Ameche.
I'll consider all of them somehow.
thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Good luck.
There's no such thing as a cheering song with him.
I don't.
From him.
Your hands are shaking.
You're too happy.
You're shaking too much.
He's coming to the show.
I got it.
I'm going to do my best now.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll do my best.
It looks like you've been drinking here.
It's soaked
I'm happy
Good morning
We'll be cheering for you... us.
We are Hinatazaka 46
Please give us your best wishes.
Our dream is to perform here at Miyazaki Sanmanin Stadium.
It's our dream to perform live here at Miyazaki Sanmanin Stadium.
We want to appeal to the people of Miyazaki
We want to appeal to the people of Miyazaki.
I came to the camp today.
I'm a big Giants fan.
I've been rooting for the Giants ever since Mr. Abe was healthy.
This is your first season as manager.
How do you feel about it?
I'm sure you've coached before. I'm sure the coaches have had more experience
than they did then.
I'm about the first one.
I feel like I'm good to go.
I'm hungry.
Is that a reply?
Thank you very much.
I know you have been coming to Miyazaki every year for many years.
Do you have any recommendations for places to visit in Miyazaki?
Miyazaki?
Not in proportion to the number of years I've been here.
Gyoza (Chinese dumpling) shops...
Oh, gyoza! Delicious!
Miyazaki gyoza.
I used to say on TV.
The guy who runs the place came out.
It used to be a restaurant that could only hold about 10 people.
But now it's a reservation-only restaurant.
So much so, that the announcement was...
What?
Gyoza.
Gyoza? Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Stickers at the camp.
Stickers! Oh, my God! So many!
Thank you very much.
I'll take it.
I'll do all kinds of ceremonies.
I'd love to.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's a great way to get people to come.
I'll do my best.
Well, good luck.
Thank you very much.
I'll be rooting for you. I'm rooting for you.
Yes, sir.
Where am I?
This is Ogura-san.
Here we are.
It's famous for its chicken nanban.
I hear it's very good.
Let's go.
Let's go!
I'm looking forward to it.
Wow, it's nice. It's nice.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
Wow, you picked it out.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Hi. - Hi.
Please do.
Nice to meet you.
You have a lot of great signatures.
This is the man.
And the menu?
It's as red as MOTHER 2.
MOTHER2
Oh, Ogra, I really want the chicken lambur.
Decided?
Oh, aren't you guys having the Chicken Lambur?
I'll have the Chicken Lambur.
I'll have an Ogla's Chicken Lambur.
Two.
Mango drink.
Oh, we're all gonna share.
I'll have a mango drink.
Three, please.
That was delicious.
I made a mistake. That was delicious.
I'm already eating. I'm already eating.
I got hungry. I said it was delicious.
Here they come.
Cherry is here.
Insert.
Let's have a toast.
Cheers.
This is how he does it, this is how he does it.
He's the kind of guy who can elevate the other guy.
Cheers!
Rich! Rich!
Yum! Yum!
Very thick!
Delicious!
It's like smoking a mango!
It's so good!
Thank you!
It's amazing! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much!
That's great!
Chicken Nanban!
This is Ogura's famous Chicken Nanban!
Wow!
Isn't it amazing?
It's huge!
The palpals are amazing!
Dig a little.
It's so big!
It's huge!
Well, let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
- Yum! - Yum! Yum!
It's so juicy.
Bon appétit!
Your right hand is the knife. Your right hand is a knife.
Bon appétit.
I'll take it with my right hand.
You know, the take-out type.
Mmm.
Is it good?
Delicious!
It's so good!
Easy to eat.
Bon appétit.
Oh, it looks delicious!
Delicious!
Look at this!
I've never had such a mild and gentle tartar sauce.
It's so good!
Makes me want to eat rice.
Rice!
You must try this!
When you come to Miyazaki
If you eat this, you're gonna love it!
This is so good, thank you!
The great smile, emmmm.
A little too delicious.
It's delicious. But it's easy to eat. It's got this fatty texture.
It's not too sticky.
So, thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you.
Please.
Thank you for the food.
From your wallet.
Thank you very much.
Yes, I'll take it.
Thank you for the food.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for dinner.
You're welcome.
Thank you very much.
Now, I would like to go to the after-dinner dessert.
Fruit.
Yes! So, here we are!
What a strawberry color this place is!
It's Hinata Ichigoen!
Strawberries!
We're here to pick strawberries!
Well, let's get going.
These containers are also pretty with strawberries!
Yes, mashed, tebots, tebots!
Hello!
Wow! So many strawberries!
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
I heard you can pick strawberries here.
I hope you enjoy picking strawberries.
Thank you very much!
How many varieties of strawberries do you have in your garden over there?
This greenhouse has a total of 5 varieties?
We have 5 varieties.
Thank you very much!
This way you can eat as many as you like.
Wow! I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Wow! It's so cute!
It's so cute.
That's amazing.
Looks like a gyoko.
Jaiko looks good on you.
It's a gyoko.
It's cute.
If you try to take it off here, it'll come off.If you try to get it here, it'll come off.
Cute.
It's huge.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
I got an extra-large one.
Are you okay?
I think it'll work.
Big size.
Okay, hold it like this.
Put it between the pieces.
I'll put it in the bottom.
Pro.
Big.
It's about part of the way up here.
Bon appétit.
Smells great.
Bon appétit!
Thank you for watching.
Mmm!
Oh, no!
Aah! It's Mei!
I'm not May, but...
It's really sweet. Juicy. Here's my juice!
Hey, Kumi-chan, what's wrong? Did he hit you?
It's a little big.
He hit me.
Oh, my God! But it's really beautiful.
Around here. The strawberries are so beautiful!
Mipan, when I came here at a different time of the year, there were many blue ones.
I found some.
You found them? A big one?
Cool!
Isn't this amazing? It's so big!
I think I'll go for it. Can I go? I think I'll go for this one. Can I go?
Sure!
It looks difficult.
Oh, I got it!
It's good?
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Here it is!
This is really it!
Juicy and no sourness!
It's so sweet and delicious!
I can eat as many as I want!
You're so quick to choose! No hesitation!
Isn't this amazing? I'm not good at this!
Bon appétit!
It's so funny. Really. Ah, Umei-san.
Umei.
Umei Mei. I've never heard of you before.
Umei Mei. Umei Mei. Here it is.
It's very sweet.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Strawberries.
It's like you're really drinking a drink. Strawberry drink.
The strawberry juice I was talking about earlier.
The juice really has a lot of water, a lot of water.
What? My head. It's not like it's going to fit in the corner of your eye.
Shall the three of us have some?
Yes, we will.
Strawberry toast!
Cheers!
Four stars?
Four stars. Bon appétit.
Ah, the aroma is different.
The flavor is still different.
It's so sweet.
I don't know how to say it. It's lighter.
Yes, it is. It was light blue.
Yes, it was. Light blue? Yeah. Light blue?
No. Yellowish sweetness.
It's hard to tell. It's the color. It's the color.
I liked the first one.
Dreamy.
Dreamy. A dream.
A dream.
Dream? I might have liked Yume-no-ka.
I'm the second 4-star.
Four stars.
I like four stars.
I like,
Pap!
This is it.
Delicious. I like the texture.
But everything is delicious.
Yes, it is. They all have a lot of sweetness,
The water content and the texture are totally different. Sweetness.
There are different kinds of sweetness.
You should all come.
Please come.
Yum!
Miyazaki I had a great time, didn't I?
I worked hard for two days... yes... at the stadium... and seeing the Titans in camp again... it was really cool.
I thought it was really cool, didn't I?
I'd like to stand there and perform live, and I'd like to do a test, and that's what I wanted to do.
I was reminded once again that we are really in the land of the rising sun.
It's fate, isn't it? I'm looking forward to my two-day trip to Miyazaki.
I learned a lot, and it made me want to work even harder.
I will do my best to make it happen.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button.